Lesson ten. Bob visits the village market. Bob goes to the village market, a supermarket
in town. He asks Carol, the owner of the store, if she would like to sell Susan's
scrumptious cookies. Carol agrees but isn't able to tell Bob how much she'll pay him.
Thank you for making time for me today, Carol.
Don't mention it, Bob. What's up?
My wife baked these cookies from scratch. Please take one.
Hmm, chewy. These are out of this world.
My wife's a great cook.
You can say that again. I don't want to make a pig of myself, but let me take a few more.
Oink oink, just kidding.
I'd like to sell these at the village market. My customers will go nuts over these.
How much would you pay us for each cookie?
I'm not sure. I need to roll up my sleeves and figure out the finances.
Can you give me a ballpark figure now?
I don't want to jump the gun. Sit tight for now and we'll talk things over this evening.